travelandcamp.com 2011-12-28

# Privacy policy - www.travelandcamp.com

### 

The publishers of this site respect your personal data and are committed to protecting your privacy. When you register and when you make postings to our website we collect information about you. The information we collect is stored for our purposes only. The only information we collect about you is your IP address when you log on and your email address when you register as a member or when you submit a review. You will not receive unsolicited mail from us unless we need to pass on information, for instance if we need to tell you about an update to our terms and conditions. We will not pass your email address on to anyone else without your prior consent except where we are obliged by law. If you make a posting that is in breach of our terms and conditions, we can use whatever information we have about you to stop such behaviour and/or to enforce any right that we have against you.

We take all reasonable steps to keep your details safe. The information collected about you is stored on our database and we have invested in keeping your information as secure as possible.

Our advertisers, may obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example).

The information collected by them may be used for the purpose of targeting advertisements and for measuring advertisement effectiveness. If you voluntarily provide personal information in response to a specific advertisement the advertiser may collect this information and use it to respond to your request. In addition, they may combine this information with other users' information and review it in an aggregate form to understand the type of individuals who view a specific type of advertisement or visit a particular kind of website.

Cookies may be used by advertisers to enhance your experience on the web (they cannot be used to personally identify you in any way). A cookie is typically a unique number which is stored in a file on your computer that helps an advertiser to target advertisements to you, to ensure that they don't show you the same advertisement multiple times and helps them understand your likes and dislikes. This enables them to cater better to your needs the next time you are interested in their products or services. While we believe that cookies enhance your Internet experience by limiting the number of times you see the same advertisement and delivering more relevant content to you, they are not required. If you do not want the benefit of cookies there is a simple procedure to manually delete them - please consult your web browser's Help documentation for more information.

Should we decide to change our privacy policy in any way, we will post the changes here.

The Travel And Camp Team
